So, I went back to
the time of Carmelita?
Okay. I'm dead.
Miss?
What is happening to you?
You are not making
any sense!
Please! I need
to get out of here!
You!
What's wrong with
all of you?!
So, I just need to
keep Juanito
from falling in love with
me to stop him from dying?
That's easy.
Listen carefully to
what I'm about to say.
Whatever happens...
Don't fall in love with me.
Carmela, dear.
Don't forget that
you are Carmelita
while you are here.
Yeah, it's fine, Mother.
Our names sound
exactly the same, so...
I can handle it.
Juanito!
My god!
Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
Juanito?
I just need some fresh air.
But it is not allowed.
What?
It is not allowed.
Why?
Even though I’m
the one with her?
Pardon me, Sir Juanito.
But you are not
accompanied by anyone else.
We will bring Nena,
the househelp.
We’ll just stroll around.
Let me handle it.
No! I’m not ready yet!
I'll be reminded of all the
embarrassing stuff I did!
Miss!
Wait a moment!
Where are you going, Miss?
Why are you following me?
Miss…
last time I
checked, I live here.
Wow, arrogant huh?
Where are you going, Miss?
Now I get it! That’s why
Carmelita fell for this guy.
Juanito’s too handsome.
Miss?
Is there… a mango
tree around here?
Where can I find the mango tree?
Why are you asking?
I cannot say. Just because.
Don’t tell me…
Your father will surely kill you
the moment he discovers this.
He’s a killer? Don Alejandro?
I mean, my father
He will search the whole world
just to find the man
who disgraced you.
Excuse me?!
Hey!
I’m not pregnant!
Where the hell did
you get that from?
Forgive me, Miss.
According to the
books I’ve read,
the mango fruit is
the usual craving
of pregnant women.
Hello?!
I’m not pregnant!
I don’t even have a boyfriend.
I'm not seeing anyone.
I'm not in a relationship!
A boyfriend you said?
Maybe that’s why
you’re too grumpy.
Because you haven’t
fallen in love yet.
Not only judgmental
but nosy too!
Miss.
Miss Carmelita,
To be honest, you amaze me.
Despite all that
you’ve said to me,
you still have the
confidence to face me.
Hello? That’s exactly
why I’m avoiding you!
It’s you who’s
always following me!
Juanito, I mean… Sir Juanito.
Do you know the saying,
“when something
embarrassing happens…”
“It’s much better to
pretend that it didn’t happen.”
I think I never
heard of that one.
On what book did you read it
or whom did you hear it from?
Father told me.
You know, Miss…
I remember you
haven't thank me yet.
And what for?
First, I saved you.
Second,
I didn’t tell Mother
Olivia that you wanted
to escape the
convent that night.
And third…
I am here to accompany you.
Honestly,
I hardly say thank you.
but since this guy is persistent
and is smiling genuinely,
I still won't do it!
Whatever you say.
But if it’s a mango
tree you’re looking for…
We don’t have any in our garden.
But I know a place
outside of our estate.
Should I trust him?
He’s a stranger and
might put me in danger.
I’m not gullible!
Miss?
Don Mariano,
we’ll take our leave since
it’s getting late in the night.
Then I will not
stop you, Alejandro.
Where are Maria and Carmelita?
Josefina, I saw
you talking earlier.
Where are Carmelita and Maria?
Maybe they went
looking around the house.
But surely, they’re
about to return.
Father…
Mother…
Are we going home now?
Where is your sister?
Where is Carmelita?
Are we there yet?
Almost.
So, I guess he’s an
expert at escaping too.
Why didn’t you
just ask the servants
to pick some mangoes for you?
- Since your condition is so delicate…
- I told you, I’m not pregnant!
Are you an addict?
Miss…
what is the meaning of
the word you just spoke?
Addict?
Oh, when someone
says, “you’re an addict,”
It means you're a gentleman
Well then… I am
indeed an addict.
I can handle myself.
You can go.
Miss, I cannot allow that.
The road is dangerous.
You might get hurt.
What? Is this the pick-up
line boys use in this era?
Believe me,
I can protect myself.
Can’t you see this?
Even when frogs are
jumping at your feet?
[Carmela screams]
[Juanito chuckles]
I hate those things!
Frogs!
I thought you fear nothing?
The frog almost had a heart
attack because of your screams.
You’re concerned for that frog?!
Let’s just go!
- We’re here.
- What?
Are we really here?
Then where are they?
Huh?!
Who’s “they?”
Are you sure we're
in the right place?
This is the closest mango
farm outside our property.
And this is the
most fruitful tree.
OMG. What if Maria already
went back to the mansion?
Carmelita!
Juanito!
What is the meaning of this?!
What are you two doing here?!
Pardon us, Father.
Don Alejandro…
but this doesn’t mean anything—
Are you saying there’s
another meaning
to this secret meeting
between you and Carmelita?
Well, Juanito?
Is that what I teach you?
Father…
Oh my gosh…
I forgot that it’s not
normal in this era
for a man and a
woman to be together
without anyone else around!
Is he abandoning me?
He wouldn't help me?
This is what I do
when I want to escape
from my Dad’s scolding.
I hope it’s effective here too.
Carmelita!
Carmelita, dear!
- My daughter…
- Oh, dear.
Carmelita must be tired.
It is important she
gets some rest.
Mother Olivia is right.
Carmelita was
probably too exhausted
from their long journey.
Then you go home without me.
We’re going to discuss this
unbecoming behavior of these two!
Josefina, let’s go.
- Josefina!
- Help me with her.
Are you okay Carmelita?
Alright, this is a safe space now.
But I sure want to get
back to my own time.
My dear…
Don’t be upset about
what your Father said earlier.
He got carried away.
And I know for sure,
your Father can’t be
mad at you for too long.
She’s just like my Mom…
It's weird that I have
a mother in this era.
But it’s fine.
In a way, I want to experience
having a mom again.
I haven’t seen you
in months, dear.
How’s your life in Manila?
Oh no. What should I say?
It’s okay.
“Okay?”
Is it a term often
used in Manila?
Shit. Mother Olivia’s right.
I should probably
shut my mouth now.
It’s like…
just fine.
Very good. That’s what it means.
Give it a few more years
and you’ll learn so
much more in Manila.
And you’ll be serving
the Lord as well.
I was just thinking
about your beauty
and capabilities…
If only you could share
them to your future family,
If you would have one.
But still, it’s honorable
to serve the church.
What? Carmelita was
studying to be a nun?
Did she want to follow
the footsteps of Josefina?
Okay then, take a rest.
And tomorrow, don’t forget.
Ask forgiveness from your father.
What did you and
Alejandro talk about?
We had a calm conversation.
But he didn’t like
what happened.
Juanito told me that
he and Carmelita
don’t have any
kind of relationship.
He just accompanied her.
It doesn’t matter.
You know how people would think.
Alejandro is worried about his
youngest daughter’s reputation.
What does he want to happen?
You know.
Juanito is a good child.
He has always followed
whatever you ask of him.
This time, I only ask that
you put your son’s
happiness first.
We need to talk to Juanito.
Miss Carmelita.
Wake up.
Miss, it’s time to wake up.
- Miss…
- What?...
Jenny, Emily.
Please, leave me alone.
I’m still sleeping.
Pardon? Miss, my
name’s Theresita
Your mother has asked me
to wake you up.
You’ll be late for
the first mass in town.
[Carmela grunts]
Is this a joke?
Who the hell is this girl?
Miss, your bath and fresh
clothes are ready as well.
How old are you?
Ahh…
Oh, I’m 13 years old, Miss.
13? In this tender age,
girls in this era are
already working?
When I was 13, the only
thing I do is use my phone.
I will assist you in
bathing and changing.
No need.
I want to be alone.
I’ll do it on my own.
Just leave the clothes there.
Yes, Miss.
I’ll put them here.
I’ll just call you
if I need help
putting on make-up.
Make-up?
Pardon me, Miss.
What is that?
It’s, uh…
Do you have any spare fabric?
I’m gonna “make something up.”
Oh, I do, Miss.
I’ll just get it downstairs.
I still can’t believe
that I'm the girl
in the painting
Am I even in my own body?
OMG! Is that Juanito again?
Shit, they might see us!
Carmelita!
Carmelita, what’s
with the sudden rush?
I need to poop.
She needs to use the toilet.
Can’t you hold it a bit, dear?
I would like to go
around the market.
I apologize, Mother.
Doña Soledad?
Doña Juanita.
Good morning, Doña Soledad.
Ladies.
Miss Carmelita.
What is this guy smiling about?
Good morning,
Doña Juanita. Juanito.
Excuse us,
but Carmelita and I must go.
The mass has just finished.
Aren’t you coming
to the feast later?
Carmelita couldn’t hold it in.
She needs to go now.
What?! That’s the same as
telling them that I need to poop!
So embarrassing!
Carmelita? Carmelita!
Have you met with
Juanito last night?
I heard he’s back
in San Alfonso.
So that’s why he’s not
answering my letters.
Have you heard the
rumors about Sir Juanito?
They caught him last night
with the youngest
daughter of the Montecarlos.
Miss Carmelita?
Yes. Rumor has it that
they have long been
secretly seeing each other
without their
families’ knowledge.
Is that so?
Miss, would you
like to buy these?
These are lovely.
Made from gold.
This is very cheap.
Maybe you’re interested?
Buy from us please.
It has only been six
months since my brother left,
but there are already rumors
that you are seeing someone new.
This was the girl who slapped
me back in the convent.
What’s her name again?
And what brother?
Who is she talking about?
Be careful of the words
you speak, Natasha.
Why?
Is it not true?
That the honorable daughter
of the Montecarlos family
was caught with a man
in the middle of the night.
With no chaperone in sight.
What did you think
people would say?
Damn, rumors spread
fast in this era too.
I apologize, Natasha.
But it seems like your knowledge
is based purely on speculation.
I know it's true
Talking to you is such a waste
of time
Oh, gosh. I can’t
understand a thing!
Let's go Carmelita
Gosh. So mean girls
exist in this time too, huh?
Don’t take offense
with what Natasha said.
She’s naturally mean-spirited.
Just be careful in
dealing with her.
She’s just like
Shae. A war freak.
And look at that.
Mean girls aren’t the only
ones existing in this time.
Womanizer spotted!
Is he smiling at me?
Carmelita!
It’s been so long since
we last saw each other!
I have so much
to share with you.
Maria, can I take Carmelita
from you for a while?
We’ll just chat.
Alright. I’ll just
walk around then.
I won’t be long, brother.
We’ll just chat.
Alright, Sonya.
“Brother?” So, they’re siblings.
I judged them too early.
Am I a judge now?
Sure, Sonya.
Just let me know if
you’re ready to leave.
I hope you’re
feeling relieved, Miss.
Damn! He had to
remind me of that!
-Come, Carmelita.
I’m glad and thankful that
I listened to your advice.
Oh… is that so?
Good to hear.
I don’t even know what
advice Carmelita gave her.
The heart can be taught indeed,
just like you said.
At first, I don’t want
to marry Ignacio.
But because of what you said,
my mind has changed.
I am now happy that
Ignacio became my husband.
I promise to myself
that I will never be that corny
when I fall in love.
Oh, by the way, Carmelita.
Are the rumors true?
That you and Juanito are
getting to know each other better?
No, of course not!
He was just helping me look for Maria
And then, people
saw us together,
sparking rumors.
What I meant was,
Don Mariano saw us.
So, we got reprimanded.
Next time, be cautious.
Things like this
spread like wildfire.
I also heard that Helena’s
back in San Alfonso as well.
I think you should
bear her in mind.
Carmelita.
We’ve been friends for so long.
I hope you won’t
hurt her feelings.
I know you did not mean
what have happened
That’s why I feel that
it’s better for
you to talk to her.
To clear things up.
What? Did Carmelita
do something wrong?
And I have to
apologize in her place?
What do you mean?
Have you forgotten?
Helena has feelings for
Juanito
What?
Someone has a crush on
Juanito aside from Carmelita?
I hope you won’t
forget all the things
Helena did for you and Leandro.
Not because they’re siblings,
but because she wants
you to end up with Leandro.
So confirmed!
There’s something
about that Leandro.
He’s Carmelita’s
secret boyfriend.
Father,
Mother.
You wanted to talk to me?
Rumors are already
circulating around town
about the incident last night.
Juanito, I believe that you
and Miss Carmelita don’t
have any kind of relationship.
But…
But Don Alejandro would
not be pleased about it.
He wants you to clear
Carmelita’s name.
Clear her name?
You don’t mean…
Marry her.
We will not force you.
The decision is still up to you.
That’s okay, I think.
Carmelita, prepare
the crock pots.
How should I say this?
If there's an oven here,
I've already cooked
lasagna for them
Mother, I’m not feeling so well.
I don’t think I can cook today.
Oh, dear.
But I already taught you and
your sisters how to cook
this special
caldereta?
Aside from that,
you are the one who
must cook this today.
Doña Soledad…
We haven’t finished the
decorations in the drawing room
when the butler
lost consciousness.
Alright,
Carmelita, carry on cooking.
Come, follow me.
What should I do now?
Carmelita.
Are you still not feeling well?
If I’m the one to cook today,
will that stop you
from being upset?
Really?
I want to apologize.
I forgot that there’s something
going on between
you and Juanito.
Let’s forget about that.
Just help me with this.
Miss, let’s fix the
ornament in your hair.
Your mother will scold me.
She specifically told me to
take extra care in grooming you.
She’s too much. We’re
just here in the house.
Dear…
Whatever you hear later,
just keep smiling.
The guests have arrived.
Don Mariano.
Sir.
- Good morning.
- Let’s go.
- Good morning to you as well.
- Come in.
- Good morning to all of you.
- Juanito, good morning.
- Good morning.
They’re the important
guests?! What the hell?
Don Mariano…
Let’s talk about the
upcoming wedding
that will bind our families
into becoming one.
Wedding?
Who’s getting married?
Don Mariano.
Everyone knows that
our maiden daughter
is always here at home
since she doesn’t really know
how to socialize
with a lot of people.
We give her the utmost
importance and care.
But now,
I am giving the hand of my
youngest maiden daughter,
Carmelita Montecarlos…
To the second
son of your family.
Dear boy… Juanito.
I give you my
daughter to take care of.
Oh no... damn it.
Just my luck.
He’s even sitting
in front of me.
My friend,
I wanted to suggest
doing the children’s wedding
by the end of February.
On the 29th of February?
That is also the
birthday of Carmelita.
Oh, shocks. It’s
going to be a leap year.
Grandma Carmina said it
would also be the wedding day
of Juanito and Carmelita,
when Juanito died.
And then Carmelita took
her own life after a week?!
And now it’s happening again!
We also want them to get married
in the church of San Alfonso.
We are going to take
care of everything.
Isn’t he gonna say
no to this wedding?
Maybe he asked
something in return?
Or he’ll get a huge inheritance?
What do you say, Miss Carmelita?
Carmelita.
Doña Juanita is
asking you a question.
What is it again, Doña Juanita?
I would also like to know.
How many children
do you want to have?
Are they tripping?
Do they seriously want to know
how many children I want to have?
Maybe Carmelita
haven’t decided yet
since she is still very young.
I just want to say that
I think it’s for the
better if she would bear
many children for Juanito.
Isn’t that right, son?
You’re quite right, Mother.
Why are we talking
about children?
I feel like I’m gonna be sick.
For me, a dozen
children is enough.
Goodness, Sergio.
Isn’t a dozen a bit too much?
I suggest ten children.
Eight children are
what I’m recommending.
Gosh, what’s happening here?
Is this a bidding?
What do they think of
me, a pig for breeding?
What do you think, Juanito?
Miss Carmelita?
- Seven.
- Nothing.
My god, my blood
pressure’s rising.
What do you mean, dear?
You don’t want to
have any children?
Oh good Lord.
Carmelita, take back your word.
A woman who doesn’t want
children is said to be cursed.
What I meant to say was,
nothing would be
more happier than…
Having a husband like Juanito
and giving birth
to seven children.
[relieved chuckles]
Juanito seemed to
fall in love with you
because of the caldereta.
From now on, he will
always crave for your cooking.
If only Juanito knew that
I don’t know how to cook.
He’s in for a future where
he’ll turn into skin and bones.
By the way, I heard
something about you.
I heard Carmelita is quite
adept at playing the piano?
Isn’t that right, Sonya?
Don Mariano, our family
is very proud of Carmelita
because of her
talents for music.
If that’s the case,
then maybe you can play
even just one song for us?
Oh no! What should I do?
I don’t know how
to play the piano!
Let them hear you play.
Showcase your talent.
Do not be shy.
Ah, Carmelita!
Play that song you always
play for me and Helena.
My goodness!
I don’t even have a clue what
Carmelita plays for any of you!
Lord, please bring
forth the rapture and
let the earth swallow
me whole. Now, please.
Shocks. I’m sorry,
Carmelita, but I need to do this.
Very well!
Good thing I still remember something
from music class back in elementary.
Carmelita knows that is not
the piece I was talking about.
But maybe she’s not
just feeling well tonight.
Apologies to you all.
Come.
I’m still sleepy.
But I have to learn how
to cook from Mother Olivia.
They might ask for me to cook
Caldereta every now and then.
I can’t rely on
Josefina forever.
You must stir it just right.
It shouldn’t be lacking.
And it shouldn’t be too much.
The food won’t taste
good if you rush it
or if it’s overcooked.
You know, Mother Olivia,
if only we have a
microwave here,
I can do that quite easily.
But…
well, let me do that.
I don’t have any choice.
- Dear.
- Yes?
Just so you know.
- I’ll be leaving by noon.
- What?!
I must go back to
the convent in Manila.
But… no!
Mother Olivia, you
can’t just leave me here.
You’re the only one
who understands me.
I’ll just come with you.
Calm down, dear.
Next week, you can
come back to Manila.
Gosh. One more week?
One week of nothingness.
No wifi,
no cell phone.
- No TV.
- Dear.
Those things don’t
exist in Manila as well.
But at least you’re there.
I’m not gonna be all alone.
And what if a problem comes up?
No one will save me.
Good thing you’re aware
that you stir so much trouble.
That’s why you need to fix
all the problems you made here.
Make sure no one would suspect
anything about your
uncanny actions.
Can’t I just come with
you, Mother Olivia, please?
Please! What if you leave
and come back to
the modern world?
I’ll be left here all alone!
I cannot leave
unless you finish
your mission here.
Don’t you worry, dear.
For now, I’m the only
one who understands you.
But as the days pass,
many will be on your side.
Carmelita,
Madre Olivia.
Father.
Get ready. We’re
going out later.
Alright.
Oh my… where could we be going?
Didn’t you bring
any flowers, child?
What?
Your friend is sick, isn’t she?
That is why I asked you to come
so you can visit Helena.
And there’s also something
important I need to discuss
with her father,
Captain Vicente.
Here.
Give this to Helena.
Good thing your mother
was able to prepare flowers.
Alright.
- Good day, my friend.
- My friend.
I see you brought
your youngest along.
So she can visit Helena as well.
Good day, Captain Flores.
Alright, dear.
You may go to Helena’s room.
I’m sure she’ll be
glad to see you.
Alright.
Where’s Helena’s room anyway?
Can I help you, Carmelita?
Shocks! It’s Natasha!
The mean girl we
encountered yesterday.
What is she doing here?
Is she Helena’s sister?
Are you still hoping
to receive a letter
from my brother?
Pardon me, Miss Natasha.
Captain Vicente has asked me
to show Miss Carmelita
to Miss Helena’s room.
Whew! Thank you, Universe.
That’s a sign for
me to avoid a fight.
Watch your steps.
What is she saying?
I don’t get it.
You might fall, and I...
can't wait to see it happen.
This girl is so
screwed up in the head.
Maybe trashtalking is
not yet invented in this era.
Shall we go, Miss Carmelita?
Thank you.
What was your name again?
I am Laura Isabella, Miss.
Shocks! Did I hear that right?
Isabella? That’s our last name!
Miss Helena, Miss
Carmelita is here to see you.
How are you?
What are you doing here?
This is for you.
I just wanted to see
how you’re doing.
Me? You’re worried about me?
What for?
You and Juanito
are set to get married.
Helena, the thing is…
Seems only yesterday
that my brother was your lover.
And now, you turned to Juanito?
You know well how long I had
these feeling for Juanito, right?
Believe me.
It was an accident
when they caught us
under the mango tree.
I was just looking
for my sister, Maria.
How can I be sure you
have no feelings for Juanito?
Are you sure of your
plan Miss Carmelita?
Shh!
They might hear my name.
Don't say my name.
And Yes! I am sure of my plan.
No one can stop me.
It's nice and clean
in his bedroom.
Wait, Miss!
Do not look!
I know that you don't want
this wedding to continue, right?
I will help you.
Helena has feelings for you.
Why does Helena seem
more important to you?
Is our wedding not
important to you?
You don't have to come here.
I just wanted to see
and be with you, Miss.
Good morning, Sir Jaunito.
Good morning, Trinidad.
- Carmelita!
- Yes?
What are you still doing there?
We have an important
place to go to.
Did you not receive?
The letter that Helena sent?